Anders Jensen









804.335.6054

jensenal27@gmail.com

<u>LinkedIn</u>

<u>Portfolio</u>

SUMMARY OF EXPERIENCE

Anders is an Administrative Professional with over three years of Facilities Management, Event Logistics Coordination, and Administrative Support experience. Over the last year, he has gained experience in software development, focusing on building web applications with React, and has developed multiple projects for Booz Allen Hamilton's Innovation Center.

EXPERIENCE

Assistant Manager, Workplace Experience

Booz Allen Hamilton, (January 2019 – Present)

- + Design, modify, develop, write, and implement software systems to facilitate employee and guest interaction with technology throughout the space
- + Assist with launch of visitor check in and metrics system through third party vendor
- + Manage quality control by maintaining 100K budget and managing vendor relationships
- + Act as liaison to CBRE facilities leadership representing Booz Allen Hamilton's first innovation office: The Innovation Center

Concierge, Innovation Center

Booz Allen Hamilton, (January 2018 – Present)

- + Manage on-site access responsibilities, telecommunication, and organization of physical space including scheduling orders, stocking, and keeping inventory of food and drinks and office supplies
- + Complete weekly metrics and create and update PowerPoint dashboard on high level information for leadership
- + Update digital signage with daily events and meetings
- + Create a 3-week outlook in Excel for internal website, send reminders and serve as on-site support, register visitors and issue site badges according to firm policy

Logistics Coordinator, Conference Center

Booz Allen Hamilton, (July 2016 – December 2017)

- + Execute meeting and event logistics and planning in three Conference Center locations
- + Accountable for all meetings and event logistic responsibilities including: audio visual, facilities, and security coordination
- + Analyze and present meeting and event data to leadership
- + Assist with the implementation of new firmwide tool used for scheduling meeting and event space and workspace
- + Lead information sessions on-site and via teleconference for internal staff during launch

EDUCATION

Old Dominion University

Bachelor of Arts in English Literature (2016)

SKILLS

HTML CSS JavaScript React NodeJS Git